what's up in this video I'm going to
show you what's working right now with
Instagram ads why we like Instagram ads
how we got here and what's the
difference between this other types of
meta ads now again for those of you that
haven't met yet my name is jerem my
Kowski and I've been in the online
marketing sales space for the last 22
years which means I've been doing this
for a while and I've seen the ABS and
flows of what works back in the day we
used to sell CD and DVD products and I
built multiple businesses to over $10
million one of them to over $20 million
a year did that along with my mom Sandy
Kowski if maybe you've heard of her name
and we did so with Facebook ads and
Facebook ads is something I've taught
for a long time and I still use Facebook
ads uh but we found a trend that has
occurred that's shifted with using
Instagram ads that Instagram ads are
starting to convert much better and so I
want to walk you through very simply in
this video why that is I just put
together a brand new training it's on my
website over Jeremy grow.com again if
you're watching this after the time this
video is released it might not be up
then but right now if you're watching
this when it's brand new it's over here
it's a brand new Instagram ads training
it's 42 minutes long and I break down
step by step how to set up your
Instagram ads the right way now what we
found was last year between about
February to April something shifted when
it came to using Facebook ads they
weren't working as good as they
previously did and I'm I'm talking like
a massive shift across the board with
everybody that I was working with and it
became like everybody was like oh my
gosh why is this happening why is this
going on part of it I also think was
economic I also think it was ramping up
and gearing up towards the uncertainty
of the election in the United States I
think had a lot to do with that I think
that was a big Factor last year but here
we are now 2025 we're we're past that
and yes is the economy any better no not
really but are people buying more
coaching yes absolutely they are and
Instagram ads is the way that we're
getting people to do so getting leads
for less than 50 cents a lead and so I'm
going to show you kind of the difference
and how that is and why that is so with
Facebook ads traditionally we would go
into Facebook ads we would set these up
and we would launch them on the Facebook
news feed now there's a difference
between the Facebook news feed right
here if you're scrolling scrolling
scrolling on
Facebook
versus over here on Instagram and the
behavior of people is different how
people act how they respond how they
look at posts even how ads show up
there's less words in the ads and so
what we did was we studied a number of
different funnels a number of different
people as far as what are they doing
with their ads we did a lot of trial and
error testing I went through every
course that was out there unfortunately
most of the courses that were out there
on this topic went that great my
training is Bar None still better than
anything else that I found and I'm proud
of that fact because that's what we hear
from people all the time is they went to
a bunch of other mentors and trainers on
these topics and it didn't quite get
them to what they wanted so I'm going to
show you simply the Difference Maker in
the Instagram ads that made the biggest
difference so here's one of the things
is that right now something shifted on
the internet called the ticktock
ification of the internet and we've been
talking about this for a while now about
how the tiktock ification on the
internet has changed people's attention
span people have a lower attention span
when they find you online and so because
of that they are less likely to watch a
Long training or join you for a long
challenge or even just buy from you
something simply because you have
something of value so a lot of people
are going based on an old way of
thinking that they think that that is
how they are going to get more clients
is by doing it the old school way the
way that doesn't work and so the new way
is much shorter much simpler and it's a
lot more it honors where people are at
but it also plays with the algorithm and
what it does to people so one of the
things a lot of people don't realize is
that the algorithm on social media get a
little nerdy with you here it it creates
this sort of up and down version of do
dopamine where it has a high dopamine
and a low so what you'll notice is on
the algorithm you have stuff that makes
you happy really excited and then you
have things that anger you and make you
upset and what this does is this
actually puts you into a slight Trans
State so this is actually what all the
algorithms on social media do they're
very good at this they're designed this
way the algorithms use artificial
intelligence to read and to tell based
on how you personally respond
they the algorithm quote unquote most
people don't realize this is personally
designed for every single user on the
platform so it's a different algorithm
for every single person and that's crazy
kind of scary kind of
weird but what'll happen is when you run
ads it's going to find a group of people
that have at least similar algorithms
similar versions of the algorithm the
algorithm is very smart
it knows what people's desires are it
knows what they're looking for it knows
what they want the most YouTube also has
a very similar algorithm maybe you found
this video on YouTube and was
recommending it to you probably because
you've been looking for Content around
this topic and so what we have to do is
we have to honor that fact of how that
works and we have to ride that wave with
the algorithm so one of the biggest
mistakes that I noticed that a lot of
coaches and mentors make is that they
Don't Ride The algorithmic Wave they
don't know how they've never been taught
this so I'm going to teach you something
that's going to help you long term with
this is that you have to whenever you
create something if you want to get
clients not if you want to bring
transformation to people not if you're
wanting to coach people at on a great
level not if you're wanting to change
people's
lives just for the purpose of
advertising marketing and getting
clients
sidebar here you're still going to
transform those people's lives you're
still going to help those people but one
of the mistakes I know that mentors and
coaches make is they make content based
around the needs of what the marketplace
needs what their clients need what they
need to learn not what they actually
want and so what you have to do is you
have to play the game of the algorithm
and give it what it wants number one
okay and so one of the ways that we can
test this out is what I like to do is I
will actually create content organically
and if something starts to gain organic
traction then I will start promoting it
as an ad however here's the problem I
have a following of people already that
I can do that with if you're just
starting out you don't already have a
big audience and a bunch of people who
engage with you that strategy pretty
much goes out the window and so that's
where Instagram ads comes in to where
you can basically test that out very
simp simply very quickly and very easily
to see what people are responding and
reacting to and so it's twofold is what
we're looking to do with these types of
ads number
one the ad needs to get
people's
attention without
attention nothing
works and you could go into a whole
topic about how social media is a
playground for narcissists and it's all
about any attention people who crave
attention and that's all it is
listen
sure however if you're a business owner
and you're wanting to use it to get
clients you also still need to play the
same game that the algorithm prioritizes
and get people's
attention now I'm going to tell you this
I'm actually not the greatest person at
getting people's attention I'm gonna I'm
GNA give you a great example of this a
cute
uh baby well I guess if I'm holding my
babies in a video or a photo I get a lot
more attention on my posts than I do
when I'm not um if I post a sports car
or I post if I post me playing video
games I get like nothing okay if I post
a piece of content on social media on
Instagram that's really transformative
and going to give people the the the
secret sauce that's going to get value
it doesn't get a lot of attention in
fact even here on
YouTube and without a thumbnail and a
good title maybe this video has a good
title thumbnail or not I'm not sure
we're you know we test out those
different things and what determines
that but the video won't get a lot of
views even if it's the best content in
the world so the problem is that the
best content doesn't always get
attention you tracking with me just
because it's good content just because
it's transformative just because it's
going to help people does not produce
the attention that you need so what
you're looking for is you need attention
grabbing
visuals combined
with
Punchy
headlines and you want to get straight
to the point of what outcome you're
going to provide for people you want to
speak directly to where they are at so a
tension grabbing visual with a Punchy
headline of some kind something that is
is a problem that they're having and a
direct solution that you offer and then
you want to encourage people to
comment so the idea is is this this is
three-fold that happens when they
comment the algorithm really really
likes when people comment on your
content so what you're doing is in your
content you don't want to give away all
of the
answers this is another problem that
people make they give away all the
answers in one piece of content like
it's that one opportunity that they have
to meet people and unfortunately like
this is very immature this this comes
from a place where like
we're we're we're we're so Desiring to
impact people that we're just I just
want to give it away to them all at once
so that they get it and in fact you got
to play the long game here just a little
bit with the algorithm where you tease
the content you still give some value
you give a little a little bit of value
you tease the
content with a Punchy headline to get
people to comment to get the
full piece of content so a a a a version
of what this might look like is this
right
here if I go over to my Instagram I'm
going to show you a perfect example of
this
okay this one is more content driven
huge key for in stagram super
transformative content that could help
people not a lot of comments not a lot
of Engagement since last night but it's
great I'll leave it up but this one
right here has eight comments people
that have already
commented I'm having fun there's some
fun music and before you're like well
Jeremiah I couldn't dance on social
media I can't dance either yet here I am
right there just kind of doing a little
jig like this because it's simple
because it's easy and then I have a
Punchy head line right here with a
simple call to action comment this word
simple right here and I'm talking about
the result that we're getting and how
everything is shifted so I've teased the
content right here and now that works
really really well running that as an ad
then goes even further because people
start commenting and then the comments
start pushing it further in the
algorithm the algorithm then gives you a
cheaper cost because people are
commenting and then those people what
are they commment for or they're going
to get that training that I mentioned to
you so again you want to have some kind
of lead Magnet or training attached that
people are going to sign up for I think
that's something that a lot of people
Miss is they don't have a lead magnet
they're just trying to go straight to
client with this having some kind of a
lead magnet to get people on your email
list is super helpful so this is what
when people comment it sends them here
and then there's a full training on how
to actually set these up and how this
all works and so this is the shift that
has happened online with Instagram ads
away from what we were doing with even
the talking head style of video the
video ads that are working and I'm going
to show you exactly how to do them what
to do what to say how to write them and
all of that in that
training what works is something that
grabs people's attention has that Punchy
headline and I'm going to show you how
to build out those and how you can use
AI to actually create those Punchy
headlines go grabb that training if you
can please I'm going to put the link in
the description below this video as well
here on
YouTube or if you're watching on
Facebook because I do upload it to
multiple
platforms and so when you get your
Instagram ads
up you it it might not seem like oh this
is a piece of content that's going to
generate all these results and things
like that but it speaks to the desire
that the person has you're tapping right
into that desire that somebody
has and you're letting them know that
you have something that they can get
access to that is connected to what
their desire is so you're going based on
the desire that somebody has somebody
has a desire to get results they know
that they've been struggling and they
want a proven system to get the results
in their business so then I'm able to
lead people to a training that I put
together that they have to sign up for
with their name and email address to get
those
results and that system right there my
friends especially when you attach
Evergreen marketing to it especially
when you can do it without having to
show up live is a system that is
duplicatable that you can do and I
haven't even told you the best part when
people comment on those
posts you can set up a thing there's an
app called many chat that helps you do
this very simple to set up very easy to
set up I'll show you how to do that as
well in our programs
and you can it will direct message
people the link and then because of that
you can then send a followup to those
people to re-engage the
conversation and generally if somebody
engages with you in that followup you
can start to get to know them learn what
they're going through learn why they're
struggling figure out triage the the the
scenario and from there you can close
those people as sales and you can get
turn leads into sales and it's a lot
simpler and a lot easier than some of
the crazy funnel hacking clickfunnels go
high level way that people have been
doing it and it's the way that we're
teaching everybody to do inside of our
programs and so again if you want to
know the best way to do this go check
out that training that I put together
the Instagram ads training that goes
deeper into this Instagram ads are
working way better way cheaper and are
more accessible right now than Facebook
or any other for typee of AD platform so
go check that out and I'll see you in
there talk soon